<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</title>
    <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/api/</guid>
      <description>Rest API Source code for all the REST resources can be found from package com.spotify.reaper.resources.
Ping Resource  GET /ping  Expected query parameters: None Simple ping resource that can be used to check whether the reaper is running.   Cluster Resource  GET /cluster
 Expected query parameters:  seedHost: Limit the returned cluster list based on the given seed host. (Optional)  Returns a list of registered cluster names in the service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/community/</guid>
      <description>We have a Mailing List and Gitter chat available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuration An example testing configuration YAML file can be found from within this project repository: src/test/resources/cassandra-reaper.yaml
The configuration file structure is provided by Dropwizard, and help on configuring the server, database connection, or logging, can be found at:
http://www.dropwizard.io/1.1.0/docs/manual/configuration.html
Reaper Specific Configuration Settings The Reaper service specific configuration settings are:
segmentCount:
Defines the default amount of repair segments to create for newly registered Cassandra repair runs (token rings). When running a repair run by the Reaper, each segment is repaired separately by the Reaper process, until all the segments in a token ring are repaired.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>