<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</title>
    <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/building/</guid>
      <description>Building Install Packages Debian packages and RPMs can be built from this project using Make, for example:
make deb make rpm  Building JARs from source The easiest way to build is to use the following make command:
make package  To build Reaper without rebuilding the UI, run the following command :
mvn clean package
To only regenerate the UI (requires npm and bower) :
mvn generate-sources -Pbuild-ui</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/docker/</guid>
      <description>Docker Docker and Docker Compose will need to be installed in order to use the commands in this section.
Building Reaper Packages with Docker Building Reaper packages requires quite a few dependencies, especially when making changes to the web interface code. In an effort to simplify the build process, Dockerfiles have been created that implement the build actions required to package Reaper.
To build the JAR and other packages which are then placed in the packages directory run the following commands from the top level directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/install/packages/</guid>
      <description>Downloads and Installation The current stable version is 0.6.2 :
 Deb Package RPM Tarball  The latest beta version is 0.7.0-beta-25082017 :
 Deb Package RPM Tarball  For a docker image, please see the Docker section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>