<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</title>
    <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/astra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/astra/</guid>
      <description>Astra Backend To use Astra (Cassandra managed service by Datastax) as the persistent storage for Reaper, the storageType setting must be set to astra in the Reaper configuration YAML file. In addition, the connection details for the Astra cluster being used to store Reaper data must be specified in the configuration YAML file. An example of how to configure Astra as persistent storage for Reaper can be found in the cassandra-reaper-astra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/cassandra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/cassandra/</guid>
      <description>Cassandra Backend To use Apache Cassandra as the persistent storage for Reaper, the storageType setting must be set to cassandra in the Reaper configuration YAML file. In addition, the connection details for the Apache Cassandra cluster being used to store Reaper data must be specified in the configuration YAML file. An example of how to configure Cassandra as persistent storage for Reaper can be found in the cassandra-reaper-cassandra.yaml.
storageType: cassandra cassandra: clusterName: &amp;#34;test&amp;#34; contactPoints: [&amp;#34;127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/h2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/h2/</guid>
      <description>H2 Backend To use H2 as the persistent storage for Reaper, the storageType setting must be set to h2 in the Reaper configuration YAML file. When using H2 storage, the database will be automatically created under the path configured in the configuration YAML file. An example of how to configure H2 as persistent storage for Reaper can be found in the cassandra-reaper-h2.yaml.
storageType: h2 h2: # H2 JDBC settings url: jdbc:h2:~/reaper-db/db;MODE=PostgreSQL user: password: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/memory/</guid>
      <description>In-Memory Backend To use in memory storage as the storage type for Reaper, the storageType setting must be set to memory in the Reaper configuration YAML file. Note that the in memory storage is enabled by default. An example of how to configure Reaper with In-Menory storage can be found in the cassandra-reaper-memory.yaml.
storageType: memory In-memory storage is volatile and as such all registered cluster, column families and repair information will be lost upon service restart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/docs/backends/postgres/</guid>
      <description>Postgres Backend To use PostgreSQL as the persistent storage for Reaper, the storageType setting must be set to postgres in the Reaper configuration YAML file. The schema will be initialized/upgraded automatically upon startup in the configured database. Ensure that the correct JDBC credentials are specified in the cassandra-reaper.yaml to allow object creation. An example of how to configure Postgres as persistent storage for Reaper can be found in the cassandra-reaper-postgres.yaml.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
