<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Install and Run on Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</title>
    <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Install and Run on Reaper: Easy Repair Management for Apache Cassandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Package Install Guide</title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/install/</guid>
      <description>We provide prebuilt install binaries The prebuilt install binaries for Reaper can be found on Bintray and on the Releases page of the GitHub Repository.
You can also find the installation binaries on the downloads page.
Reaper can be run as a foreground application You can run Reaper in the foreground. This is useful when developing and testing the application.
The Reaper binaries are available in a tar.gz package. Once decompressed, you can run the application using the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Guide</title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/docker/</guid>
      <description>Docker and Docker Compose will need to be installed in order to use the commands in this section.
Building Reaper Docker Image Prerequisite The generation of the Docker image requires that the JAR file be built and placed in the src/packages directory. If the JAR package is missing from the directory then it can built using either the steps in the Docker package build section (above), or in the Building from Source section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Guide</title>
      <link>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cassandra-reaper.io/install/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading from 1.2.0/1.2.1 to 1.2.2 We unfortunately had to break schema migrations for upgrades to 1.2.2 from 1.2.0 and 1.2.1. Here is the upgrade procedure for each Reaper backend:
Cassandra  Stop all Reaper instances Run the following DDL statement on the backend cluster :  ALTER TABLE reaper_db.repair_unit_v1 DROP repair_thread_count;  Upgrade Reaper to 1.2.2 and start it  Note: by doing so the number of threads for each existing schedule will revert back to 0, which will be translated to a single repair thread.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>